<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE article PUBLIC "DarArticle 0.1.0" "http://darformat.org/DarArticle-0.1.0.dtd">
<article id="article" xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink">
  <front id="front-1">
    <article-meta id="article-meta-1">
      <title-group id="title-group-1">
        <article-title id="article-title-1">Graphic Novel Thesis</article-title>
      </title-group>
      <history id="history-1" />
      <abstract id="abstract-1">
        <p id="p-1" />
      </abstract>
    </article-meta>
  </front>
  <body id="body-1">
    <sec id="heading-946d95326ae938087a9503dfa68f5264">
      <title>Script Vomit</title>
      <p id="heading-b1f1aa1adcbf8870afea73c14de1e7cc" level="1"><bold id="bold-e179aff473437afd79d74f57920c810e">NAMES IN ALL CAPS AND BOLD</bold> are placeholder names.</p>
      <sec id="heading-73cada310bd33d5375fa50e7eae2374b">
        <title>Elevator pitch</title>
        <p id="p-2d818e78f7f06aeab4b4db4043010f90">Once upon a time, about 100 years in the future, Min, a 17-year-old Water Crisis Migrant from North America, takes her first space shuttle flight to the ISS Corps, an international training program for youth interested in career class "Interplanetary Travel and Communications." As a scholarship student born into a low-ranking career class, Min must overcome social prejudice, exploitative technology, and secretive information practices to realize her dream of finding freedom and dignity in space. </p>
      </sec>
      <sec id="heading-3065e0fe5a4351b8d3724f83df9eb493">
        <title>Prologue</title>
        <p id="heading-987c3e39553c567e556eef0aa62f5b8e" level="2">It's 2105. We've poisoned all of our water, and the ozone layer is gone. But thanks to the <bold id="bold-71a0430190a0901273a2a8535a4c3fb7">SPACE CONSORTIUM</bold>'s serendipitous investment in <bold id="bold-58ef463d2b69a296d7b9054db4c81007">ESYRUP</bold> research, we can now harvest the extra UV radiation to purify our water, and filter a CO2-saturated atmosphere for oxygen. Two decades after the Global Water Crisis began, humanity is finally starting to recover. </p>
        <p id="p-2f0e2ccdeb468a240603b664f44a5363" level="2">To mark their faith in this new era of hope, the <bold id="bold-21a9019bdf26dbdc5df4e24485461f7c">SPACE CONSORTIUM</bold> establishes a scholarship program at the ISS Corps, the <bold id="bold-deb4f7fcc3265009b4bc0e7743bfd35c">SPACE CONSORTIUM</bold>'s international training program for youth interested in career class "Interplanetary Travel and Communications". The "Space Asylum Program" provides financial assistance to the families of any young Water Crisis Migrants willing to become a "scholarship student" at the ISS Corps. The scholarship means that these students may attend the ISS Corps for free, and upon graduation receive financial support for their universal-certification training of choice.</p>
        <p id="p-3">It also meant that they committed 5 years of their wage-earning years to the <bold id="bold-855b1d0a24349f1957122f0b8690a8c9">SPACE CONSORTIUM</bold>.</p>
        <p id="p-9a9647643c6b69eeee8863412b1f62ce" level="2">The "Space Asylum Program" is meant to be a living promise, that the meritocratic elite of the world, now mostly living in self-sustaining, geo-synchronous residential space stations called <bold id="bold-a57feec8f9a6e71d09c23024c3c50215">ORBIT ESTATES</bold>, would not abandon those left on Earth; that everyone would put aside their cultural and historical grievances, and that all of humanity's children would grow up together.</p>
      </sec>
      <sec id="heading-6c2940bbea2f9019aea39a54b8a660fe">
        <title>Chapter 1</title>
        <p id="p-509a9af9a8b432e6d665ae73b4b58b6e">Min is determined to get off Earth. She's tired of sterilizing everything she eats, drinks, or breathes. At least in space, your life support systems would do all that for you, and you wouldn't need to wear Headgear. </p>
        <p id="heading-4212ebc9ded16948c90bd63db7cac6fc" level="3">Min is undergoing her medical clearance exam for the ISS Corps, at the hospital in Atlanta where she and her parents have been staying as refugees for the last year. She's stressed - after a rigorous and long application process, Min was rewarded a scholarship from <bold id="bold-e473969df87c3b319512e673051eb94c">SPACE CONSORTIUM</bold>, which is the only way that she would be able to afford the ISS Corps, but now there is this medical clearance exam. Min nervously scratches her head tatoo, which marks her as part of <bold id="bold-53cc988945addba32e13479c401a1b26">FAMILY GANG</bold>, led by Min's grandmother, Mago. It's a bit red and puffy - it goes through these cycles, ever since her puberty started and she was given a <bold id="bold-1a911223ac31faaa97d8eca3fead75db">REPRODUCTIVE REPRESSOR</bold>, her head tatoo would occassionally get red and puffy, though not itchy or painful - but now Min is worried that it looks infected or dangerous and thus the head tatoo might disqualify her for ISS Corps.</p>
        <p id="p-178f1a997ec44c67ca5f67e31d0f9e69" level="3">After a standard checkup, the nurse finds that her head tatoo was slightly contaminated with <bold id="bold-c597d797f7cdea77e2589704312e781f">ESYRUP</bold>. It's rather unusual as the <bold id="bold-e2199677bdafeaab9d32866e2b6bd59e">ESYRUP </bold>seems to be several years old but is somehow still viable. After a lengthy consultation with the hospital director, the nurse gives Min a pill "to help label the <bold id="bold-140535adfb0b4e62e2fe77987b916645">ESYRUP</bold>", then scans Min's head tatoo. He then gives Min some pills that will "neutralize the side effects of <bold id="bold-fc621a695257bb1c0b3e44e917e2759b">ESYRUP </bold>contamination", instructs her to take the pills twice a day, then signs off on Min's health check.</p>
        <p id="p-2">Min says goodbye to her family and mates, who are all gathered in another hospical room. Grandma Mago tells Min how proud she is that Min will be going to an engineering institution. She expects Min to carry on the mathematical traditions of their family - both Mago and Jina are mathematicians. Mago runs casinos along the eastern coast of the Mississippi Sea, and coordinates an enormous network of diversely skilled Water Crisis Migrants. Jina developed a new branch of ansible mathematics when she and her mates turned their childhood hobby of cracking ansible transmissions from space shuttle control towers into an impressive collaborative Universal Certification Dissertation on "The theory of calculating the distance and direction of non-Large-Mass-Body ansibles in encrypted interstellar communications". Mago exclaims how she can't wait for Min to come back a Space University certified mathematician, and work for the <bold id="bold-0e27dcaad5304df6ca69a2586cc42baf">FAMILY GANG</bold> after repaying her debt to <bold id="bold-b84032b6fc8886f24cc964e1958dd4d8">SPACE CONSORTIUM</bold>.</p>
        <p id="p-a19820e100cd54eb524d4da8a4451584">Min doesn't tell Grandma Mago, but she doesn't plan to study mathematics at the ISS Corps at all. She wants to get Universal Certification in a space engineering topic and change her career classification to anything that will get her off this planet. Min thanks everyone for their well wishes and extracts herself to a smaller room down the hall, where Min's dad sits Sung-Soo is reading to Jina, Min's mom, who is being treated for cancer. Jina was diagnosed just before a raging fire destroyed their caravans. When they reached out to Grandma Mago, she had come to fetch them herself and drove them to Atlanta, where she pulled in some favors to bump them up in the waiting list for hospital treatment.</p>
        <p id="p-1374709ccbb24151e63dc6ddbb90943b">Sung-soo and Jina greet Min warmly. They ask if Min has told Grandma Mago of her new study plans. Min hasn't - she doesn't want to disappoint Grandma Mago, and she's a little scared of Grandma. Jina smiles understandingly, and reminds Min that she and Sung-soo support Min's right to choose her path at this point, pointing out that when Jina decided to study ansible mathematics, Grandma Mago was also concerned about the relevance of this newfangled tech for supporting the family and their way of life. Sung-soo reminds Min that we may never know beforehand what will benefit us in the future, so if someone is super excited about a direction, they should walk that direction with strong purpose and confident imagination. Both of Min's parents express their love for Min, and when she's ready to tell Grandma, they will support her.</p>
      </sec>
      <sec id="heading-6dbafd998c004b725cfd70bf9a0f7928">
        <title>Chapter 2</title>
        <p id="heading-d8876e8e2c01350f18933943429cc6cf" level="2">Min boards a space shuttle for the first time, even though she's spent her whole life seeing the ponderous, enormous vehicles draw condensation traces in the atmosphere daily with their entries and exits. On board she meets other successful applicants to this year's ISS Corps cadet cohort, but there are nervous whispers of the high rate of drop-outs during the first year: 48% last year. The space shuttle automatic PA system announces a "health and safety during space travel" speech in a chirpy voice as they prepare to exit the atmosphere. Everyone is given barf bags. The shuttle exits the atmosphere, and many of the cadets who had never experienced zero-G before get super naseous, including Min.</p>
        <p id="p-d0af55a957ea006b85dca8f77442fc6b" level="2">The PA announces that they will arrive at their next stop, an <bold id="bold-070a05b8570ee7d7ea94878f03268dec">ORBIT ESTATES </bold>shuttle station, in 2 hours. Min struggles to get comfortable in her seat (the safety straps dig into her shoulders), and tries to nap in order to banish her nausea.</p>
        <p id="p-76caaf6db1b9753a9ccca951eff7c700" level="2">Suddenly the front end of the shuttle bursts open - apparently there are more passenger compartments! A group of cadets wearing the body piercings indicative of <bold id="bold-22cfd2df994d3a41643cd5ab33d80749">MONASTIC CULT </bold>enter, swimming easily in the zero-G and accompanied by their <bold id="bold-c6dc37e13b886eb26723b316bd0adc65">ESYRUP DAEMONS</bold>. Min realises that everyone in her compartment were either <bold id="bold-de75e0a00d3ee6964156e33171c1372c">NORMIES </bold>("mod-virgins") or <bold id="bold-ccd8239875fe809040f4a9a7ca741080">GANGIES </bold>("head tats"). <bold id="bold-7a1c67a2835f83759701a766d2530fc7">GANGIES</bold>' head tatoos are made from normal ink but designed like QR codes - they contain encrypted information for Augmented Vision, which is now a standard feature of <bold id="bold-ae78ea0d9d9c26ad905e72e6ab655814">ESYRUP</bold>-enhanced eyeballs<bold id="bold-5b228b8e5fca8f678479e264e89c03df"/>. Only the very rich and powerful have <bold id="bold-a1c06c352c9e3f64147bda09b32c803d">ESYRUP </bold>tatoos, subdermally injected on their skulls and along major nerves, which basically turn them into cyborgs, humans who have incorporated their personal digital computing capabilities directly into their nervous systems.</p>
        <p id="p-a2b3854a0ac4ab1db1ff80c01f255cd0" level="2">But all post-Water-Crisis <bold id="bold-965a69e973532e8ca124089af3292b6f">ESYRUP </bold>is "harvested <bold id="bold-12fd9ee42161e3541d86081434d02c35">ESYRUP</bold>", which can be injected into and calibrated to biological tissue once for best effects. The second morph tended to be slower and stiffer, and usually by the third morph most harvested <bold id="bold-2a80e0965b4b7ed4deb7cce855d4cf5d">ESYRUP </bold>has had its last reconfiguration. Though the formula for viable, living <bold id="bold-e0f7d62673b30b269b982a2723c9e3ed">ESYRUP </bold>was once freely available, by the time the Water Crisis was over the formula was lost from the public record, and now everyone buys harvested <bold id="bold-57a1fb9f808ba2f89f8491172191436f">ESYRUP</bold> from <bold id="bold-d4e2cbbf9f66105c87b0b34227f102a3">SPACE CONSORTIUM</bold>. </p>
        <p id="p-2d821b1ae6b7c0bb71b8919cbf04cd41" level="2">The group of <bold id="bold-f2454c8b81b88cfdfd39157559b884c3">MONASTIC CULT </bold>cadets encourage everyone to unbuckle and float in the zero-G, as it will ease the nausea and be more comfortable. The <bold id="bold-6bddcc47c444f63d5b8ee14d3c52c10f">MONASTIC CULT</bold> cadets also let them know that the shuttle has a cafe compartment with snacks and drinks where other cadets were hanging out for the journey ahead. Everyone heads to the cafe compartment. Min meets more cadets, many of whom are at the viewing ports to watch passengers from the <bold id="bold-ad1d690938fd4e978e968ab93c01e62a">ORBIT POD</bold> shuttle station board the shuttle.  After boarding is complete and the shuttle un-docks, the PA system announces that their remote pilot will be switching their shuttle to auto-pilot at this point, and that this shuttle's rendezvous with <bold id="bold-2f2978e8848a9282f198cdfea18f0662">GEMINI</bold>, the ISS Corps geosyncronous station, was expected in 1 hour. With a click, the PA system switches over to playing soft, pre-Water-Crisis jazz. </p>
        <p id="p-c4e2b25cef7db2176badc9a9a544a97d" level="2">The cafe compartment doors open and the newest passengers enter. They all sport <bold id="bold-a2441d34b5174f802a21b145a269c2eb">ESYRUP </bold>tatoos, and most of them immediately form their own circle at an empty cluster of tables. Some of them strut through the rest of the cadets, expressing disdain for the <bold id="bold-d2ff0bd2ca802695268e31620e68fa9f">GANGIE</bold>'s non-<bold id="bold-69f10dda4fb9aae401cb7d89804a366b">ESYRUP </bold>head tatoos, pity for the "mod-virgins" still wearing Headgear, and deep-seated prejudice, sometimes masked in begrudging respect, against the <bold id="bold-03073c15b32c3395703f38bee350d709">MONASTIC CULT </bold>cadets.</p>
        <p id="p-e2d7deecfd9c42e6a6e30f0a5b6cb59a" level="2">Rhee, a <bold id="bold-0c791ea772dcc0526c4c27edbcaa4f44">NORMIE </bold>cadet, gets sick all over Rajue, a haughty cadet with <bold id="bold-33980be66fce088f17da1080323fab23">ESYRUP </bold>tatoos. Rajue is furious and starts verbally abusing Rhee, who is still trying to keep her stomach under control. Min gets upset by his unreasonable reaction and steps in to tell Rajue to lay off, but then he turns his anger to Min instead. Min, who grew up in tough urban neighborhoods and is a bit hotheaded herself, got in his face, and things start getting physically violent.</p>
        <p id="p-67f7392872dde2c26384fe4f4f46bf1c" level="2">Asoka, a <bold id="bold-61c239ff8c4d7b558f346d429c249a44">MONASTIC CULT </bold>cadet, steps in and tells them both to calm down. <bold id="bold-27b9878185e926ffade46ff807c28a33">IRI</bold>, Asoka's <bold id="bold-b38ba567d6299b389e7142e0d96ea703">ESYRUP DAEMON</bold>, who looks like a flamboyant cuttlefish but is about the size of a medium-large dog, cradles the sick Rhee in its arms while Asoka faces Rajue, who decides to escalate and injects himself with <bold id="bold-681a3ab0fc8724f8038796e5330170a0">WHAMO!</bold>, a popular "mood enhancer" made of adrenaline and instant muscle toner. Asoka fluidly and skillfully pins and subdues Rajue. She tells everyone that she, <bold id="bold-7e0d3d63d347bc3a02b3a5927a7991d3">IRI</bold>, and Min were going to leave with Rhee to help her feel better for the rest of the journey, and Rajue was going to stay in the cafe compartment and behave himself. Rajue brushes himself off and huffily disappears into the crowd of cadets.</p>
      </sec>
      <sec id="heading-806e13a41ecf1222d9f68a5df8003eaf">
        <title>Chapter 3</title>
        <p id="heading-fd32f47dabcc67c636e23b2a1c962bee" level="2">Min and Asoka help Rhee back to her compartment, where Rhee digs through her bags for an anti-nausea pill. Rhee insists that she's fine, she just needs some quiet and good grief, what she'd do for some sparkling water. Min reveals that she'd nicked a couple bottles of sparkling water from the cafe. The girls open bottles of fizzy water over toasts to their newly forged friendship. Rhee confesses that she is terrified of space travel and going crazy out in space, but the <bold id="bold-a183ceddd2e0ee2e7852a5ed3e4962a2">SPACE CONSORTIUM</bold>'s scholarship was the only way she could afford to change her career classification - her parents are morticians in a part of Southeastern Europe where the Water Crisis brought on an epidemic of dengue fever, and Rhee doesn't ever want to see that many dead bodies ever again. Honestly, says Rhee, it wouldn't have been so bad if they hadn't kept running out of <bold id="bold-4db9e66cc41ed33d53a0382a8f0da377">ESYRUP</bold>, which Rhee's parents sometimes had to beg for or steal in order to keep up with their duties of processing dead bodies. </p>
        <p id="p-d872b6a821ce1a30cf527883af805e52" level="2">Asoka is from a very different family - her parents are agricultural researchers on a <bold id="bold-500361cf91be02dfd44af83eff68f043">GREEN HAVEN</bold> in Ireland, and very deeply involved in the <bold id="bold-8b4ed35dcbaacde63a7be2bf03afcaf4">MONASTIC CULT</bold>. Asoka had a very physically demanding upbringing - farming, capoeira with her father João, climbing trees and building treehouses. She has been training to be a kinetic linguist, or one who can communicate using movement and can understand other species' movement languages. Thanks to the intimate connection that Asoka, like any other member of the <bold id="bold-20f6a75996d9513f39a81d26d5b020df">MONASTIC CULT</bold>, shares with <bold id="bold-7b2381349afee99716169e4760b4ed03">IRI</bold> via her body piercings, she and <bold id="bold-1344c1ff8f9415572258974c34f681ad">IRI </bold>can together rapidly and fluidly change Asoka's skin color, similar to the natural abilities of cuttlefish. </p>
        <p id="p-897cde728b2ca8f4aa3df02b89cfd5e4" level="2">Min shares how all of the women in her family are mathematicians, and how her <bold id="bold-0c826d5a54c2d5803fdc721555fb3b27">FAMILY GANG</bold> relies on mathematical algorithms for their collective living. But Min's father, an artist and activist, has also inspired in Min the belief that space travel should be accessible to all, especially the Water Crisis Migrants on Earth who have no home. Min wants to be free, able to fly from planet to planet without anyone's permission, in a space ship she has built and knows how to maintian, with a crew she can trust to live and work with. So she wants to learn how to build and maintain space craft. Rhee points out that that is a huge topic and she'll probably have to specialize, but Min insists she wants to know "everything" about her space craft. </p>
        <p id="p-5acfb6f214a4d7fee8c067c3f2c5c061" level="2">As they approach the <bold id="bold-2d4d43fee9bacc3e363cc04eaae76539">GEMINI</bold>, all three of them marvel at its design. The final part of the journey takes them on a slow drift over the station as the shuttle matches its velocity with the station.</p>
        <p id="heading-4cb12550b3bd34acb720d10b791263c4" level="2">The shuttle finally docks with <bold id="bold-f1dc52749b342e2eab0c9cb6e4934ba3">GEMINI </bold>station, as the PA system announces that all cadets must check their entry documents for their crew assignments. Asoka is assigned to <bold id="bold-bb8cd6bdc8f3563988d09ed3d796531e">CIRQUE DU COSMIQUE</bold>, Rhee to <bold id="bold-7f4ef5cf0157322e400b88fb59116a80">MENDELEEVERS</bold>. Min looks for her crew but finds "Undecided" on her documents. PA system calls, "If you are an Undecided, please report to Docking Bay Door 0813." Asoka, Rhee, and Min promise to find each other later. They step out into the docking bay to see the whole school lined up, rank and file, ready to greet the newcomers. "Welcome, muskies!" they roar in unison, as they snap into the ISS Corps cadet salute. "Muskies?" "It's because you all still smell of Earth!"</p>
        <p id="p-91520ae5762b019cb83f5ab2030ccc61" level="2">Min reports to Docking Bay Door 0813 and finds a small group of cadets. She is greeted by third-year cadets Zalo, of the <bold id="bold-e9e90e22bea05ae55ecfc46b855fe3bd">INFRADESTRUCTORS </bold>crew, and Jheri, of the <bold id="bold-61401599af12c382522b1c26be300868">CYBERPHILIA </bold>crew. They both volunteered to show around the Undecideds, which places their crews at the front of the line for who gets to host Undecideds first.</p>
        <p id="p-aaa7573d1a0be665452fabe08ced9021" level="2">Zalo and Jheri explain that the <bold id="bold-95672f9a7ee8dac0f0cfe90d7c7be4d0">UNIVERSAL PUBLIC RECORD</bold> didn't have enough data on Undecided cadets, and so the school's sorting algorithm was unable to place them in a crew. They would spend the next week getting to know each of the home crews and would need to pick a homecrew by the end of the week. Day 1 would be with <bold id="bold-2407921e0929581cf944d5af3d9e4385">INFRADESTRUCTORS</bold>, Day 2 with <bold id="bold-3b7cff235730d8494af54a6bae00ef6c">CYBERPHILIA</bold>, Day 3 with <bold id="bold-5ce8a18d90b3159787b604b55d3a8292">CIRQUE DU COSMIQUE</bold>, and Day 4 with <bold id="bold-b55a642097c426cf7941afa85fc0e3d5">MENDELEEVERS</bold>. Day 5 and 6 would be with the home crew of their own choosing, and could be different for each day. On the morning of Day 7 they must submit a ranked list of all 4 crews, listed from most preferred to least preferred crew. Each home crew also submits a list of all Undecideds, ranked according to how much they would like to have an Undecided join their crew. Reps from each home crew meet with these lists and negotiate, and anyone who doesn't end up on a crew must leave the school. </p>
        <p id="p-bad780431974cb8829dea53c590bdbd7" level="2">Zalo and Jheri hand out non-disclosure agreements that all of the Undecideds must sign. The home crews will be sharing with them craft/trade secrets that are normally never revealed to anyone not part of that crew. Because the Space Asylum Program is so new, and the ISS Corps never had Undecideds until the program started a few years ago, the school's home crews haven't had time to modify their induction week procedures. </p>
        <p id="p-4f602d6c92b0cd0cc453db6e1d0da748" level="2">Zalo then shows the Undecideds a day in the life of the <bold id="bold-30ffeca88c90fd6a3446f176f37bf619">INFRADESTRUCTORS </bold>crew. They take apart a <bold id="bold-5df771b91a35b0041042c36b6695d8fc">POCKET UNIVERSAL SCANNER</bold>, a device that can obtain measurements of the electromagnetic, chemical, and biorhythm properties of any creature or object. Min bonds with many here over the democratization of tech and the social implications of the ban against basic research of <bold id="bold-6a18356fbc6ad657d2794ba224af78d7">ESYRUP</bold>, which is so prevalent and used by so many and yet kept proprietary. The recipe was originally made open source by the inventors of <bold id="bold-2af17a1290e3bb049ea5608d7ea533cb">ESYRUP</bold>, but that was before the Water Crisis disrupted the global digital information infrastructure, among other things.</p>
        <p id="p-29e98aa8fee690a62bd8c5dd6175cea7" level="2">After a whirlwind first day, Min and the other scholarship students report to the <bold id="bold-a0c9262c067a8e154d49bfdd416c2443">HEAD OF SERVICE CREW</bold>, who turns out to be a <bold id="bold-e9e2c4732a278bc5dc402c51280e11cf">GANGIE</bold> named <bold id="bold-69ca5cd551fe852c87c2c566f08b8695">PQ</bold>. Min and <bold id="bold-c8afc62c21ab16731ddab53ab08e76ee">PQ </bold>instantaneously bond even before realizing that Min's grandmother once saved <bold id="bold-bbcecfb89c6654fb380f8d705c84f69b">PQ</bold>'s mother's life. <bold id="bold-c6f04b7dd4110421ec608c3f953569a7">PQ </bold>reassures Min that if she's ever feeling overwhelmed by her schoolwork, <bold id="bold-3927bf48744ffedabf268c0b25ba98ec">PQ </bold>will put Min on the front security desk shift, which is the quietest shift, so that Min can do schoolwork while fulfilling the service crew requirements of her scholarship from <bold id="bold-a62601d2d2779528da06e32ed6187143">SPACE CONSORTIUM</bold>. <bold id="bold-c79b1486649fc41cc345232b3e68bda8">PQ </bold>asks if Min plans to study mathematics. Min tries to come up with a lie, but then her <bold id="bold-75cc7042840e7ca0492505300dda6169"/>head tatoo flares up again, only this time it causes a sharp pain in her head. <bold id="bold-9f75f76195a3e51d425cdf8bdd042aaf">PQ </bold>notices Min's exhaustion and pain and tells her to get to bed at once.</p>
      </sec>
      <sec id="heading-8c4d3ff8f6d2d82fa82aa1fa393be290">
        <title>Chapter 4</title>
        <p id="heading-195d8ef92df1877bf1a53f0c5b7060ad" level="2">On Day 2, Jheri shows the Undecideds a day in the life of the <bold id="bold-0f596afed114bca3b5a7b80da2ea4538">CYBERPHILIA </bold>crew. Min bonds with many on this crew over a shared love of anime, live improvisational music, and <bold id="bold-1e4fd026e0e2a075c23ef10535a60fcf">ESYRUP DAEMONS</bold>, as many <bold id="bold-2caa2192437b8a54f685149bc6dc4f82">GLOBAL MONASTIC CULT </bold>members tend to end up in this crew. Many muskies with <bold id="bold-c0bc12ccb00010bd6211e78e84252fb1">ESYRUP </bold>tatoos also end up in the <bold id="bold-a2c3fe8070ec1076fc95eec235fc2bdd">CYBERPHILIA </bold>crew, including Rajue, who loudly wonders how any mod-virgin will be able to do anything worthwhile in the <bold id="bold-6041e66686c226f7cb6c21fb1044455e">CYBERPHILIA </bold>crew. Jheri firmly reprimands him for his disrespectful comments, and he begrudgingly apologizes. </p>
        <p id="p-a968d32c1c4dfad13890bb6de536e306" level="2">Jheri teaches the cadets how to use the laser atomic manipulator (LAM), which allows them to perform surgeries so precise that they can cut out a 1cm cubed volume out from deep inside of a living animal without causing bleeding or needing stitches. Jheri is currently considered one of the top cadets at ISS Corps, in large part for her incredible dexterity and precision with the LAM. She has already begun her Journeyhume training with one of the ISS Corps professors, who invented the most recent version of the LAM, which is an order of magnitude cheaper and more portable.</p>
        <p id="p-a34242edb7c6bc645b71041bbdad53d9" level="2">On Day 3 the Undecideds are dropped off at <bold id="bold-3a02605ead845bfb2ddde7284c9f2426">CIRQUE DU COSMIQUE</bold>, where 3rd-year cadet <bold id="bold-8db012260c69273d067c7f30e81b9070">GIARMO </bold>is leading the day's physical training. Min quickly falls in love with the <bold id="bold-157cb4cc37a016e055059c6fbcede68f">CIRQUE DU COSMIQUE</bold>'s training and performance spaces, their lovingly maintained aquariums and terrariums, and their movement focused lifestyle and mentality. After a morning of rigorous drills, they break for water and fruit before they play games on the playgrounds the crew builds for themselves, a combination of capoeira, parkour, and numerous East Asian martial arts traditions. By lunch Min is exhausted but exhilerated. In the afternoon, Asoka brings Min to her "Animal Husbandry in Space" course, where teacher <bold id="bold-4df02d8f8dc2b57db7a86330882689c9">ADI</bold>, a professor on the teaching staff of "Health and Well-being in Space" during the semester, entertains them with stories of research animals on space vessels escaping their designated areas. After the lecture they watch <bold id="bold-01e1fd89ebf8d4490734586c0983d18b">IRI </bold>play with biological cephalopods in the aquaculture tanks, and Asoka reveals that she's been teaching <bold id="bold-e34b2f90a54a81e283e51a9270f2c915">IRI </bold>to change not just her color, but also her texture and general body shape. Asoka demonstrates her kinetic linguistics skills by having a brief conversation with the cephalopods in the aquaculture tanks. </p>
      </sec>
      <sec id="heading-c4a8cfe3b9c4248d243fe9cf73bdf3be">
        <title>Chapter 5</title>
        <p id="heading-798f362278487e0e48c05383cae3c9d3" level="2">It's Day 4, and the Undecideds are with the <bold id="bold-d7dc91aa1b9408ffde855ca35e074510">MENDELEEVERS</bold>, where ISS Corps alum Tross is giving a demonstration of space welding tools as fellow <bold id="bold-2c3631fabf4929d126f357f483e77a2d">MENDELEEVERS </bold>2nd- and 3rd-year cadets play rapid fire rounds of "What if...in space?!", in which a situation is invented in which something breaks out in space, and no internet is available, and very few technologically optimized tools are available, and thus one must macgyver a solution using un-networked tools. Tross's <bold id="bold-6484e09618e6d9db0acecedf4140c72f">ESYRUP DAEMON</bold>, a midnight black, silky, sinewy cat named <bold id="bold-e83ee50a2af14d1be76e6890ed9e37c3">INQBI</bold>, alternates between curling around Tross's shoulders like an adorable, purring scarf, to gliding through the shadows like a silent, hazel-eyed wave of death and destruction. Min finds Tross's teaching style incredibly exciting and asks such eager questions that Tross and Min continue chatting over lunch, where Min also finds Rhee. Min and Rhee become fast friends with <bold id="bold-c95e7b1177c22260efc078f07110be38">INQBI</bold>, who shares their fondness for fried cheese. Min's head tatoo flares up again, and Tross asks Min if she's alright. She explains that she might have some mild <bold id="bold-258f189b8d1596a97f4527f47bc6396e">ESYRUP </bold>contamination, but she's gotten some pills to help with it. Tross asks her several probing questions about the pills and expresses concern over some of the active ingredients. Tross then excuses himself, saying that he needs to return to Space University now.</p>
        <p id="p-6140bfbc8f5d0cd6f5b3261c330ecfed" level="2">After lunch, Rhee introduces Min to Oana, another <bold id="bold-128ab2d6d4e1c43783979b5a7b0f8d07">NORMIE </bold>and a scholarship student in her 2nd year, who has become an expert at blowing microscopic bio-compatible <bold id="bold-0d6e4182deef045c3d47188a349916c3">ESYRUP</bold>-infused glass filaments, which can be gently embedded subdermally to create programmable, interactive "mod-makeup". It's not quite like <bold id="bold-99571e1a5bd627bad5c5f7b41113492d">ESYRUP </bold>tatoos - the <bold id="bold-e6adeaef51a74005a3058ff058bcd6e5">ESYRUP </bold>in the glass filaments have only limited input from the biological tissue and are programmed prior to injection. Oana shows them how to verify each piece to certify it safe for subdermal injection. While they work, Rhee teases Min for her fascination with Tross. Oana reveals that Tross was a muskie during the same year as Zalo and Jheri, but he is the first and only cadet to graduate in one year - most students take the full 3, and occassionally someone graduates in 2 years. Tross is now a 2nd-year journeyhume at Space University as an independent space welder, but he returns to the ISS Corps for the first week of the year, to be part of the initiation week and hold workshops and demonstrations for the <bold id="bold-2dce4281f5a37f55983fcd360b7b2301">MENDELEEVERS</bold>. Rhee also confesses a fascination with understanding the fundamental workings of <bold id="bold-29ae3923466163dfec5ffc6149dc8295">ESYRUP</bold>, and encourages Min to ask Oana about her <bold id="bold-b90150f1a9bd330f17cd0210d013c572">ESYRUP </bold>contamination. Oana listens to Min's symptoms, examines her head tatoo, and suggests talking to someone from <bold id="bold-3931f97887d6aee87bebe85692da2324">INFRADESTRUCTORS </bold>to help her learn more about her pills. </p>
        <p id="p-5025dde691ba11532a6a7cc236e25ded" level="2">On Day 5, Min spends the morning with the <bold id="bold-50789e7bed06ea74ead13f6e2e031e84">INFRADESTRUCTORS</bold> crew, trying to de-black-box her pills. They make some startling discoveries with the <bold id="bold-7b4e60b9f63e8ac135547ce7879cf85b">POCKET UNIVERSAL SCANNER</bold>, which make Zalo wonder if Min should stop taking the pills altogether. </p>
        <p id="p-445c9599ec45e8533fc62f641eda0a93" level="2">At lunch, Min catches up with Rhee and Oana about her morning session with the <bold id="bold-61d08dce4ae7eb6a3b27eb0d1c7deff2">INFRADESTRUCTORS</bold>. After lunch, she joins Rhee for a workshop on "Common chemicals on space vessels with surprising properties", where Rhee proves to be a natural at chemical alchemy. After the workshop, Min spies <bold id="bold-2cf776dbfbbebc62007a143a6eb619a4">INQBI </bold>disappearing around a corner. Follwing <bold id="bold-d054c21e6a48314009430b9c4dde7341">INQBI </bold>in the hopes of running into Tross, she steps into a workroom where she sees what looks like a delicate metal flower on the workbench. She goes in for a closer look, when Tross suddenly appears and asks what Min is doing. He tries to encourage her to leave, but Min is fascinated by the flower and wants to learn more about it. Tross tells Min to forget the flower, claiming that it is a failed experiment that will get incinerated anyway. Min asks to take the flower, under the logic that she will happily investigate the "failed experiment", especially if no one else wants it. Tross refuses to give it to her and tries to physically remove her from the room, but of course Min doesn't stand for that. As their grappling becomes more earnest, one of the surveillance cameras catches the violence and an alarm goes off. Tross grips Min hard and says, deadly serious, "Min, if you value your life, leave right now." Utterly shaken, Min flees.</p>
      </sec>
      <sec id="heading-ead2e81dbff3a0064c890481508332ab">
        <title>Chapter 6</title>
        <p id="p-dd9f188bd43df6fa8b2920d25cdc19a5" level="2">Min spends Day 6 with Asoka and the <bold id="bold-a476adbd494034e032f92404f3bf2905">CIRQUE DU COSMIQUE</bold> crew. She had slept in Asoka's sleeping structure the night before, she was so confused and frightened by Tross's behaviour. She and Asoka had discussed it until late into the night, and now, the next day, she just wants to shut up the questions in her head with blindingly difficult physical challenges, so she and Asoka work on space swimming drills until they reach lunch time, exhausted. Everyone is super excited by how quickly Min's space swimming is improving, especially Asoka, who has been training space swimming since childhood and is eager to involve Min in her experiments in multi-partner synchronized space swimming, which could be a new way to accomplish certain build and maintenance tasks for space vessels in orbit or during space travel. Min spends a wonderful lunch with Asoka, <bold id="bold-d3b14280564101efd67e9e4073e1d820">GIARMO</bold>, and numerous other admiring cadets, discussing the history of space swimming. </p>
        <p id="p-458e343014699671ac07ab3f5addfc82" level="2">As lunch ends, Zalo and Jheri come to find Min. They ask her if she feels able to make a ranked list of home crews, and which crew she feels the most connection with. Min confesses that she is horribly torn, she loves every crew for different reasons! She goes on to Zalo about the things she loves about each crew and what she feels she could learn from all of them. Zalo and Jheri exchange a look. They sternly tell her to study her feelings more closely and come to a decision, as she will not be allowed to learn craft/trade secrets outside her home crew's career class qualifications. And if she cannot find a home crew to join, she will have to leave the school. </p>
        <p id="p-115c201c9720ca523499450ee7d720c8" level="2">Min is left feeling miserable. She doesn't want to leave the ISS Corps, but she's also pretty sure that she won't be able to build her affordable and accessible space craft with the knowledge and skills from just one crew. She runs into <bold id="bold-3d4edc3a26422733bc892fb86e61cb78">ADI</bold>, who asks her about her upcoming decision. Min finds herself telling <bold id="bold-2990075e9eebd39bd0c6cc12aaa8749b">ADI </bold>everything, from her father's activism and her desire to be a "jack of all space trades" to her head tatoo pain and the discoveries she had been making about the pills. <bold id="bold-99a070f676b4aeb1f320280da9e4b4dd">ADI </bold>looks strangely pleased, and confesses that he's impressed by how quickly she's been able to coordinate so many of her fellow cadets, from across different crews. He then casually hands Min a note, saying, "If you're still torn about your choice by midnight tonight...they might be able to help."</p>
        <p id="p-40868d3e54942438aeb086d83387d45f" level="2">Min waits to go to the toilet before looking at the note, which contains a cryptic message. Min spends the rest of the day decoding it, in the end recruiting Asoka and Rhee to help her. It's a location, and a passcode. Rhee thinks it's a bad idea, maybe a nasty prank, and doesn't want Min to go. Asoka insists that <bold id="bold-b01272b37185d5fe019fa762eb360a36">ADI </bold>would never be malicious, and besides she is terribly curious, and wants to go with Min to see what this is all about. Min decides she wants to at least know what sort of help is being offered, and decides to go. Rhee and Asoka insist on joining her, using <bold id="bold-788fd3f99cd858cc3af57e1257b8379b">IRI </bold>to camouflage their presence. Rhee also insists on assembling a makeshift chemical weapon, just in case.</p>
        <p id="p-296287830b62ab0a67cba818748f2387" level="2">When Min arrives at the secret location, she is greeted by two masked cadets, who coldly ask if she came alone. Min says yes, praying that they cannot detect Rhee and Asoka and <bold id="bold-dfef3daa1291328bdc4fbda450a7aa8f">IRI</bold>. The 2 masked cadets then scan her with <bold id="bold-b998109ba17465d7899599224c8d40bc">POCKET SCANNERS</bold> and find Rhee, Asoka, and <bold id="bold-14bf57989511109dcdec6ffeca519c40">IRI</bold>. There is some confusion over the unexpected turn of events, as the situation turns into a standoff. Rhee uses her makeshift chem weapon, which reveals the masked cadets to be wearing some kind of personal protective force field. Asoka tries hand to hand combat but one of the masked cadets is able to subdue her with a sheathed sword. A mysterious <bold id="bold-cd21a34971eff30dc7c4198d76b13d55">ESYRUP DAEMON</bold> pools into existence out of the shadows to subdue <bold id="bold-507bffdb4b496b66a84509e71bef227b">IRI</bold>. The two masked cadets then turn on a <bold id="bold-f4dfb2074954e7aac720cacb323b1270">SIGNAL SCRAMBLER BUBBLE</bold> and show Min the results of their <bold id="bold-8aa2bd64155050b203f68ab552db84c3">POCKET UNIVERSAL SCANNERS</bold>: Min has a government tracer in her nervous system, one that harvests biomarker data from her strangely viable <bold id="bold-657abacadb834bbf1cbcb3fa7b97242e">ESYRUP </bold>contamination and sends it to an untraceable location. Rhee, whose parents use similar, commercial scanners in their mortician work, confirms their diagnosis. The masked cadets tell Min that if she wants to stay at the ISS Corps, she needs to get the tracer removed. Min is appalled that her bio-data has been harvested for the last week without her permission, but she's scared - won't whoever put this in her come after her if they see that the tracer isn't sending sensible data anymore? Also, how could she trust masked strangers to perform this surgery on her? "Please," says one of the masked cadets, "trust us, you need to remove this tracer. It can collect stressful or suggestive mind states, save the parameters, and artificially re-trigger that mindset in you, even remotely."</p>
        <p id="p-2b25838de93aeeca120eacf8d72cafca" level="2">Min is growing increasingly frightened, and the masked cadets increasingly frustrated. Finally, they come to a decision, and take off their masks - it's Jheri and Zalo. Jheri says, "Look, I'm the best at this kind of surgery, even if I'm not yet even a Journeyhume. Please let me take this tracer out of you." Min agrees, realising that she trusts these two deeply.</p>
      </sec>
      <sec id="heading-ba9dd8c47f6d335a9d92ed44972b0812">
        <title>Chapter 7</title>
        <p id="p-1057f9c0e745002aa16470646ae8185f">Jheri carefully and painstakingly removes the tracer from Min. After the surgery, Zalo meticulously disassmbles the tracer and pockets the components. Min asks, so can I stay at ISS Corps now? Zalo and Jheri remind her that she needs to pick a crew. Min, exhausted and at her wit's end after the day she just had, explodes into a rant about how they wouldn't have been able to find the tracer, figure out what it's doing, and remove it, if Min hadn't worked with members of each crew, synthesizing their various expertises and interests to collectively solve this problem. Min's Grandmother runs a successful gang back on Earth because she can coordinate a huge variety of personalities and skill sets. Min doesn't understand how the ISS Corps will be able to prepare humans to be a space-faring species if they cling to ancient traditions of secrecy and isolated specialization. Asoka and Rhee chime in with equally furious opinions, and Zalo and Jheri ask them, do you really believe in integrating knowledge across the home crews, even though it's technically illegal? Asoka points out that over the course of this evening adventure, both Zalo and Jheri have revealed home crew-specific craft secrets with them already, and why were the two of them running around the interstitial spaces of the <bold id="bold-0d1ea3aa6bf0e3dbdf268cacad11c52e">GEMINI </bold>wearing masks and sharing crew secrets, especially when they are on different crews? Rhee suggests maybe the muskies should report Zalo and Jheri! But Min says no, no one will report anyone, but it's so obvious the benefits of sharing knowledge between the crews, so if Zalo and Jheri can't help Min then Min will ask <bold id="bold-cb18ac3fc496e8cb4e1008489f8b9179">ADI </bold>for help. Jheri and Zalo exchange a look again, then turn to the Min, Rhee, and Asoka and tell them, let's take down the <bold id="bold-2da2d1c72649017635c5851545d7ca02">SIGNAL SCRAMBLER BUBBLE</bold> and go for a walk.</p>
        <p id="p-d702cf2bd50c6b394f3e10770f2f1e10">Jheri and Zalo lead Min, Rhee, and Asoka through a maze of interstitial spaces on <bold id="bold-69ae10f1baab62aaea5ae6afeea51366">GEMINI</bold> to get to another secret room, where <bold id="bold-73140fd88898d90888be3108858ef647">ADI</bold>, Tross, Oana, <bold id="bold-cfbe87d805c80432551dd8f423d40b34">GIARMO</bold>, and a few others are gathered. Zalo reveals that these are members of a secret society here at the ISS Corps, who are trying to reverse engineer the formula for making living, self-replicating and evolving <bold id="bold-11e530e23d7605acbd3eb1979c93c70b">ESYRUP</bold>, and who have realised that they need skills and expertise from across the different home crews. They call themselves Vigilante Intergalactic Roustabout Scholars (VIRS).</p>
        <p id="p-2fd21a91fba2565f09e922acf17b0c9f">The VIRS show Min, Rhee, and Asoka their results so far. Tross, Jheri, and Zalo have figured out how to enable <bold id="bold-c961323e98a96cafda93bfac5358581d">INQBI </bold>to completely change shape and size, turning into an amorphous shadowy blob then reforming. Oana and <bold id="bold-af5aa643756c67965ec1b355173dbb31">GIARMO</bold> have started to grow plants that are spliced with <bold id="bold-f3541647f5ce06c98b8ebf1f4c4e560e">ESYRUP</bold>. </p>
        <p id="p-53f74d5fd50dbc8ef275fa49bfd09f47">The VIRS ask Min, Rhee, and Asoka to join them. VIRSs can be on any crew and are expected to study their craft well enough to bring that knowledge to the other VIRSs. Also, VIRSs are encouraged to reframe insights, which come from working in secret with fellow VIRSs, into the language and logic of their home crews, to improve the work and progress of each craft. </p>
        <p id="p-0a02fb34675570df767b05fefd4cabc3">Min is ecstatic and immediately says yes. Asoka is also very keen, ever up for a good adventure, and how can she say no to a secret society?? Meanwhile Rhee cynically asks whether she has any choice (will you just kill me if I say no, now that I've seen all this?), in the end she confesses an eagerness to untangle the fundamentals of <bold id="bold-cd22442f5f2dfbd0be55c8c021d9c027">ESYRUP</bold>. </p>
        <p id="p-516223ebb662bdaf5485ccb33297c48f">Zalo and Jheri remind Min that it is now almost morning, and she must pick a home crew. Min smiles, no longer stressed about this decision. She says, "I choose..."</p>
        <p id="p-253b5531b5b86868be14c7134e15f012">TO BE CONTINUED...in future episodes if I can get funding to flesh out the rest of this story :)</p>
      </sec>
      <sec id="heading-5e73f4e1a36eef8117bd7cbbe0079d45">
        <title>A quick history of ESYRUP</title>
        <p id="p-ddd5b5487b73450f7f3794fa685ca35c">In 2076, the UN Environmental Committee declared that all water on the planet was "unfit for human consumption." In the following decade, we lost a quarter of our planetary biodiversity and over 10 percent of the global human population died from starvation or disease, a period later referred to as simply "The Water Crisis". </p>
        <p id="heading-3c294b45e26a74b72aed00e360f27bb9" level="2">About a year before the Water Crisis, a group of bio-textile hackers accidentally spliced silicon with a fungus derived from yeast, creating a synthetic life-form that can re-assemble its atoms into tissue-like structures capable of replacing any functional unit of a classical electronic circuit (conductor, resistor, capacitor, etc). This substance, now called <bold id="bold-f12ea7ce7d37692eafe2965f9771c3aa">ESYRUP</bold>, could be spun into fabric or even directly spliced into biological structures, and it became crucial to humanity's recovery from the Water Crisis. </p>
        <p id="p-8a6278a0d8131f6280cdde97f6ac395c" level="2">When it was first invented, <bold id="bold-adb2595f9d4481e80c5058bcc7e3105e">ESYRUP </bold>was seen as a novelty material for hackers and tinkerers, and the formula for <bold id="bold-afd799dfafb208c00e04605fdb8f17ee">ESYRUP </bold>was shared widely and freely, as it could be cultivated and harvested in a way similar to a living sourdough yeast culture. During the Water Crisis, <bold id="bold-5f5ae0d8e431c3f77c8c641cf9fdeb7b">ESYRUP </bold>became the cheap, mass-produceable way to provide water filtration, vaccination against infectious disease, and even protection against harmful solar radiations. Folks with a more profiteering bent than the original inventors began breeding specialized <bold id="bold-2fb4442df0efb23ff9f6415cf6827514">ESYRUP </bold>cultures and selling only harvested <bold id="bold-4c6bae44a1bd33307aa31919bef8ba11">ESYRUP</bold>, which cannot start a viable new culture of <bold id="bold-0555c9f1eff8592f0fb1be024ab70a72">ESYRUP</bold>. A new crop of corporations specializing in <bold id="bold-f2254bc34069657d04ed7d2896ca6874">ESYRUP </bold>production and <bold id="bold-107a787712b2249df0240afa52047dda">ESYRUP</bold>-derived manufactured goods emerged out of the chaos of the Water Crisis, and these corporations began to systematically remove all recipes for <bold id="bold-a11b232f66ec440a582be22b6bf9c620">ESYRUP </bold>from the public record. Homegrown <bold id="bold-304a87a4c2268c610c6c65c229f22adc">ESYRUP </bold>cultures became vanishingly rare, and people began to forget that <bold id="bold-58c658f25165feb35abac03023d054ad">ESYRUP </bold>could in fact be grown and harvested at home. </p>
        <p id="p-768a76306446c977557acf5393dd950f" level="2">By 2100, products made with or derived from <bold id="bold-e013ce48c4919b5a0131d980da94652f">ESYRUP </bold>are everywhere, while raw, viable <bold id="bold-6c12909207f6a3bb128cbd7787744b0b">ESYRUP</bold> is kept only by the rich, powerful, or unlawful. </p>
      </sec>
    </sec>
  </body>
  <back id="back-1">
    <ref-list id="ref-list-1" />
  </back>
</article>